salliemae.com 2000-12-02

# About us: Privacy Policy

  About us  
   Corporate structure  
   Office of the CEO  
   USA Education, Inc. Board  
   SLMA Board  
   Linking to this site|  |    
**

Privacy Policy

**

The privacy of your personal information is a serious matter for Sallie Mae and our employees. As a Sallie Mae customer, a visitor to one of our web sites (www.salliemae.com, www.nelliemae.com, and www.wiredscholar.com), or a client using our business and technical outsourcing services for colleges and universities, you should feel confident that we value personal privacy. The following describes the ways we use and protect personal information.

The information contained in this privacy policy may change over time without notice. Please check back periodically for updates.

To our Web site visitors 

Sallie Mae is the recognized leader in helping students and families plan and pay for college. To maintain this distinction, we host innovative web sites (www.salliemae.com, www.nelliemae.com, and www.wiredscholar.com) and provide visitors with helpful and timely content, interactive tools and functionality.

Like most web sites, we use "cookies" to enhance your online experience. Cookies are pieces of data that we place on your computer's hard drive temporarily to enable us to identify you. The cookies that we place on your hard drive remain active only while you have your browser open, expire as soon as you close your browser, and are not used to collect and store any personal identifying information.

Our web server automatically recognizes your domain name, but not your e-mail address. We do not collect personal identifying information from visitors unless you expressly provide it to us. The information we do collect from our web sites (such as domain name, number of hits, pages visited, and length of user session) may be aggregated to analyze the usage of our web site. This information is then used to improve the usefulness of the sites.

We do not intend to collect information from children under 13 years of age. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal identifying information from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly take all reasonable measures to delete the data from the system. 

From time to time, you may access our sites through a co-branded page of one of our marketing partners or associates. We will try to indicate clearly, through prominent placement of our marketing partner's name or logo or otherwise, whether a page is co-branded. If you provide your information on a co-branded page, your registration information may be provided to our marketing partner as well. It is important to remember that if you link to a non-Sallie Mae site from www.salliemae.com, www.nelliemae.com, or www.wiredscholar.com, you will be subject to that party's privacy policy and terms and conditions of use. We encourage you to become familiar with an external party's privacy policy before disclosing personal information.

Sallie Mae does not share your personal identifying information with third-party marketers. We may use your personal identifying information ourselves, among other things, to offer our own or third-party products and services that we think you may find of interest, but only Sallie Mae, its subsidiaries, affiliates, and contractors involved in distributing the offers or providing the products or services have access to your personal identifying information. Our subsidiaries, affiliates, and contractors are required to use any personal identifying information we provide them only for that intended purpose.

If you provide us with personal identifying information, unless prohibited by law, you have the option of requesting that the personal identifying information be removed from our system by contacting us at the address indicated at the end of this policy. If you register for information, you also have the right, upon reasonable notice, to view that information and make any corrections that are necessary.

If you are a visitor to www.wiredscholar.com, and if you do not wish to receive third-party offers, you can "opt out" by contacting us at the address indicated at the end of this policy.

In our information technology systems environment, Sallie Mae safeguards your information according to industry established security standards and we routinely test our systems to ensure a high level of security.

To our education loan customers

In the course of making you an education loan or administering your education loan, it will be necessary for our employees to access information regarding you and your account. We may have collected this information from a number of sources, such as applications, transactions, or credit reports. Our employees are trained to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information and understand the importance of doing so. In certain circumstances, we are required to disclose your information, including personal identifying information, in connection with the administration of your education loan. 

Sallie Mae does not share your personal identifying information with third-party marketers. We may use your personal identifying information ourselves, among other things, to offer our own or third-party products and services that we think you may find of interest, but only Sallie Mae, its subsidiaries, affiliates, and contractors involved in distributing the offers or providing the products or services have access to your personal identifying information. Our subsidiaries, affiliates, and contractors are required to use any personal identifying information we provide them only for that intended purpose.

Contacting us

If you have any questions or comments or need to contact us in connection with this policy, please e-mail the [Internet Group](mailto:feedback-marketing@slma.com) or contact us using the information below: 

The Internet Group  
Sallie Mae, Inc.  
11600 Sallie Mae Drive  
Reston, Virginia 20193  
703/810-3000 

Back to top

|   |   
|
